;-----------|Tobi-san V2.1 Read Me File|----------------

Character Name: Tobi-San
Creator: Jerrydrizzt

;--------------------------------------------------
Whats New?:
Well Quite a bit ^^. I Got some New Sprites, New moves, New MoveSet, and Some Small Bug Fixes.
Thats just about it I Really hope you enjoy Tobi-San V2, and This May be his Last Update Sorry.
Well yeah Enjoy, and the Read me that you are Reading is Updated as well so Keep Reading ^^.

V2.1
CHanged Movelist...... Thats It XD.
;--------------------------------------------------
History (Copied from Wikipedia.com):

TOBI

Membership status: Active 
Ring: 玉 ("jewel", "ball"; "jade"; also the king in shogi) 
Ring position: Left thumb 
Partner: Formerly Deidara 

Tobi (トビ) is a former subordinate of Zetsu. 
After Sasori's death, Tobi takes his ring, position, and partner (Deidara) in Akatsuki, thereby becoming a full member.
Tobi is shown giving Pein, the leader of Akatsuki, orders, and he refers to himself as Madara Uchiha.
Tobi's personality is at odds with the standard amongst Akatsuki members; while
most are dedicated and serious, Tobi is more carefree and goofy. 
These personality traits tend to irritate Deidara, who often attacks Tobi in some way when Tobi unintentionally annoys 
him.Kisame Hoshigaki, on the other hand, appreciates Tobi's ability to brighten up their gloomy organization.
Prior to revealing himself as Madara Uchiha, Tobi uses a very formal
and correct manner of speech. As Madara, his personality and speech are completely different, 
as he speaks much less formally and is more serious and arrogant.
;--------------------------------------------------
Style:

Not much of a style Change, Hes pretty Much exactly the samein this aspect,but Heres What V1 Said

"Ok so this Character is a 3 button character. Each button has 2 attacks, and
one special. The 6 normal attacks can all be comboed and the sometimes finished
by a special. With this character you can make your own combos and play anyway you 
like. I tryed to make this character as player freindly as possible ^^."

Now In V2 You Still use 3 Buttons, but now Each Button has 3 Attacks, and 2 Specials
and as before the 6 Normal attacks are comboeable ^^.So yes Combo Freindly, and altogether
is really fun to play as i even have Fun Playing as him.
;--------------------------------------------------
Why?

"Well the other day while i was rummaging through some old sheets i came across this 
Tobi sheet, so i decided to take a break from sena and Code him Real quick. He was
Fun to code and Ended Very nicely ^^."

Ok So Just Read the ABove ^^.
;--------------------------------------------------
Movelist:

a = A key
b = S key
c = D key

D = Down
F = Foward
B = Back
 
(a) = Perform In Air

MOVESET

a = Slap, Just a melee sleeve slap
b = Kick, a forward kick knocking the opponet back, a nice combo finisher
c = Exploding Kunai, he throws an Exploding Kunai, also a nice finisher

D, a = Multi slap, Does multiple sleeve Slaps, Very sissy like ^^.
D, b = Sleeve Spin, Spins in a circle while slapping with his sleeves
D, c = Throw, If contact will toss opponet across screen, Good for finisher

(a) a = Slap In Air, Just The Slap attack in the air ^^.
(a) b = Sleeve Spin in air, Just Sleeve Spin in air >_<.
(a) c = Kunai Throw in air, Throws a normal Kunai Instead of Exploding ^^.

D, F, a = Pick up coin Special, Tobi drops his coin, he bends over to pick up and
          it causes an earthquake shooting wind at the opponet.
D, F, b = Douton Special, Tobi burrows under ground and lights bombs causing an 
	  explosion on land.
D, F, c = Summon Deidara, Deidara flies in on his Clay bird and drops his super bomb 
	  Dealing major damage If Positioned correctly ^^.

D, B, a = Douton Geyser, Tobi Goes underground and Cretes a geyser of Dirt to knock the
        The Opponet Over
D, B, b = Douton Dragon!!!, Tobi Goes Underground and summons a giant Earth Dragon Attacking
        the Opponet causing Medium Damge ^^.
D, B, C = Mangekyou Sharingan !!, Well as requested by Some People i have Decided to add sharingan.
	First off this move cant be activated unless you have 3000 Energy, and Once actvated 
        your energy will repeatedly decrease until the Sharingan Wears off. This attack may have
	some glitches, so plz comment about them ^^. 
;----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Credits: Here are credits where they are needed ^^.

SPRITE CREDITS:

Shinobi X2 - Created the Tobi Sprites, Big Thanks to him for allowing me to release ^^.
-s/s- - Created some New Tobi Sprites For Me ^^.
Neimad - Ripped the kunai, Explosion, Deidara, Wind, Ect... Thanks Neimad ^^.
Sirbrownie/Oowasi - Created the deidara bomb Sprites
CloudTk - Flame Sprites
Dimps - Sharingan Sprites
ANy other Spriters or rippers i missed, I Thank you guys aswell ^^.

CODING CREDITS:

Cyanide - Narutorials
Anjel - Looked at his itachis Air File to find something out, and He Helped With Sharingan ^^.
marvn - Sounds
Anjel - The Mangekyou Shringan Noise >_<
BladeReaperX - Pointed out Some Major Flaws That Needed Fixing
Greiver80 - Helped Me With Some All around Coding things
Anyone Else That may have helped me with Certain codes, I thank you ^^.
;--------------------------------------------------
Anything Else:

Well Copy of V1's 
"First off his sounds are not him specific because Tobi has no voice ><.
Im pretty sure all the kinks are worked out of his moves, but if you see any Problems in
anything then Please post, or contact me and i will try to improve him. Also he has a total
of 6 palletes so enjoy. Ok Well i think thats it enjoy the magical power that is super tobi ^^."

Well guys I Think thats It So ENjoy My Tobi Character I Hope you all ENjoy Him ALot ^^.
Also This May be his Last Update, But if alot of Major Glitches are Pointed out then i Will 
UpDtae him to V3, So Yeah Enjoyz ^^.




